Watcher One
Clear the scene
children go to ground
Please check external site
Sierra Kilo
No external site problems
Check the children coming up from the basement
Backpack man man on the move
Sierra kills, Sierra kills!
An explosion occurred on the ground, an explosion occurred on the ground
Secondary explosion risk
Withdrew to Bravo 4, communication ended.
Wow!
Wow
Baby, what's wrong
Where does it hurt?
uh?
no, it's okay
Dad, look at that, look at that.
uh
Stand with mom
I'll take a picture for you
Let's take a picture
Now
- One, two, three!
- One, two, three
- Wow, Doyeon, look at that.
- Wow!
and!
PD Kim
The power is off
Connected to voicemail
A call fee will be charged after the beep.
The power is off...
Today through SNS
The culprit who predicted the bombing in Kiyun City
I was caught by the police
The bomb turned out to be fake
The culprit was recently
Questions raised about the explosion in Kiyun City
After watching internet news
They said they planned a crime like this.
stated
What kind of guys are they?
what?
With a bomb in my neighborhood
Who are these people playing pranks?
Hey, how do I know that?
Because of that
Aren’t we always together?
Hey, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Uh, hello
What? PD Kim disappears?
Hey little brother
Hey, we're in big trouble.
Fake bomb?
Not that now...
Why, what is it?
I'll do it again
The strongest?
who is this?
Let's meet
Who are you?
JDD General Manager
Deputy Minister of Defense
It's Lee Geun-cheol
No, what's going on?
What about PD Kim?
I don't know, I can't contact you.
No, I
I saw a part-time comment spot on the video.
I contacted the PD.
But I didn't receive it and when I came back...
It ended up like this
yes
CCTV, hard disk
It was all ripped away.
The women’s president also came?
Why can't I come?
Is that possible?
Hey, you organize it quickly too.
Soldier?
uh?
These are the marks of combat boots.
Is it for executives?
Please give me this
I will leave a photo as proof.
I was looking for Heeja unnie before.
You planted something, right?
Uh, you know
Hey, me too now
I was thinking about that
As expected
What are you planting?
CCTV
Do you have CCTV?
Before, Heeja unni
I went out alone
I fell into a construction site
I almost got into big trouble.
Brother Chunbae was looking for me so desperately.
I planted some around the neighborhood.
Why are you talking about that now?
So when should we talk?
- Where are you?
- Here and there
Is it around here too?
Let's look at that first.
Uh, go, I'll get it, uh.
Follow me
Wow
For the laundry lady
Even things like this
It’s kind of cool, little brother.
Hey, are we neighbors or cousins for no reason?
So I'm your cousin?
You are strangely unlucky
give it
But what about the women’s president?
Do you know it's a soldier just by looking at his footprints?
Man, she's a scary girl.
707 I am a former instructor.
What?
today
When the fake bomb went crazy
I went in directly to say that it would be dismantled.
Defusing the bomb yourself?
Minseo was there
Oh, what kind of neighborhood is all special forces?
Isn’t Yonghee also 707?
Oh, he's from the 707 PX unit.
What happens later?
Hacking blah blah blah
They said he went to that unit.
Hey, hurry up, he's doing it again
Anyone can see that PD Kim
I think you're a terrorist.
Oh, those crazy people, really.
Hey, what time is it now?
I don't like the article
Are you going to catch the reporter?
It means that PD Kim hit the nail on the head.
I'm watching it now
Articles related to Magnifying Glass Media
There isn't one
Either the government controls it with an embargo, or
really secretly
It could be moving.
- why?
- huh?
Ah, it's like that when you watch the movie.
Right? When you watch a movie
That, that
Aren’t we going to get caught too?
We were the ones who reported it to PD Kim.
I also interviewed
don't worry
Yeah, don't worry
we did it all
We just
Should I upload this video?
No, not yet.
Secure the remaining footage
Let’s figure out the route.
Different camera position
Because I know everything
I collected everything today
I'll check it out later tonight.
If something special comes up, I'll post it in a message.
Then I
What should I do with this video?
I'll ask a close lawyer.
Me too here and there
I'll try calling back.
yes
What about you?
What are you going to do?
me?
Hey, this
I installed everything, this
I worked a lot
Ah...
I'm going to look around the neighborhood.
Uh, if there's anyone suspicious.
Process...
no
I'll scream
Ah!
Uh, he, hey, he has a great voice.
I'll take care of this
Hey, to investigate...
let's go patrol
- Okay, shall we go?
- Patrol, patrol...
Hahahahahahaha!
Ha...
Miss, where are you?
Wait a minute, hey
Hey!
Hey you guys
This is illegal confinement!
Here!
Call a lawyer right now!
hey! hey!
Let's talk, talk!
Where are we?
Hehe, this
Who parked the car like this?
child
Ah, this from the morning
This is really making me feel bad
What are you doing...
Honey, how do I do this?
You just need to go back and forth a few times.
Should I do it?
What millennium are you going back and forth in?
You go and open the store.
Minseo Kim, Ta
Oh, I just want taxi fare.
Hurry up and get in
- I'll come back.
- Yes
Daughter, welcome back.
Dad, hello
uh
Wow, our Namyeon is so upset.
You guys are screwed now, today, oh
mom
Yesterday's bomb, Kiyoon Middle School's second year student Aerae
The police went to their house
They said they caught it, awesome
you
are you okay?
what?
Done
Your mentality is similar to mine.
Stop looking at your phone and get down
I'm late today because I have a birthday party.
Ah
thank you for the fish allowance
Call me at 9, I'll pick you up
Yes, I will come.
Yeah
Mom, yesterday was great
one, two, three
Minmos, live livestock!
hey!
True
Oh my
A lot of things happen every day
Huh? Cell phone man!
It was okay that you got hurt at that time, right?
ride back
- I'm upset, I'm upset
- What...
Fish oil, fish oil, fish oil!
Look how good the ride is, eoyu
Did you do a good job with Photoshop?
Maybe
At the ATM explosion site
Did you see something special?
Why are you asking me that?
Every time there was an explosion, the military came and cleaned it up.
With JDD
Is it related?
I'm investigating
I don't think it's that one
Then keep researching.
Why did you contact me?
When you become a vice minister, call everyone in.
You can do it all.
Because it's not that easy
I contacted you
If the Vice Minister of National Defense is in a difficult situation,
Well, is it related to the minister?
Oh my, what is this...
‘Lee Yong-hee’
'Special Attack'...
Are you a special martial arts director?
Chi
‘Kwak Byeong-nam, stationery owner’
'HID'?
‘Namyeon Jeong, Mammoth Smart’
This lady is disarming the bomb.
Is that the lady you were fooling around with?
707 Are you the youngest instructor?
uh
What, is this from Korea University?
'mine thrower'?
What is this, is the neighborhood like this?
This guy, this guy...
Are you exempt from military service?
Well, nothing much.
to me
What is the reason for contacting you?
Bombs exploded in Giyun City
a few years ago
It was used in our military.
How was it leaked?
I don't know yet
Ah, so
The soldiers cleaned it up diligently.
But why
Does a foreigner have it?
When the ATM accident occurred
He was definitely a foreigner
That part is strange, so we are investigating.
If Choi Kang helps you...
Huh?
I'm a civilian now, yeah
It's not a mission, it's a request.
I'd like to ask you a favor too. Oh, by the way.
please don't contact me
Now centered on Giyun City
something is happening
That goes to kindergarten
Our Doyeon knows it all too.
Ah, what a surprise, indeed.
please again
Mr. Choi Kang
Where am I? uh?
excuse me!
taxi, taxi, taxi
Taxi fare 58,000 won?
Ah, this guy has a rear end, huh?
IC
Next is Kiyun City
This is news related to IT special zone development.
James Sullivan's side
Including Kiyunsi...
Uh, driver.
Please turn up the volume
yes
There are changes
I predicted there would be
Sullivan's company, Join Us Company,
To build an Asian hub
In a situation where land purchase has been completed,
There are changes in investments...
Land prices in Giyun City are rising.
People who overextended themselves to buy a house
It's not good
That's me
I feel anxious
It's spreading
In fact, Kiyun City real estate
Today's trading volume
So much so that there isn't even a single thing
I am reacting sensitively
Regarding this, Ki Yun-si
Detailed changes...
two things
I have a requirement
first
Yesterday, Magnifier Media PD Kim In-seop
You know he was captured by soldiers, right?
Vehicle number total is 60 and 6789
Surely the Vice Minister didn’t know?
Civilians, especially journalists
Without the Vice Minister knowing?
Let's find out as soon as possible
What about the second?
All records of my past erased
If the Vice Minister promises
I'll think about it too
I can check it too
I tried everything...
Yeah
You don't know either?
No, they captured a civilian.
Well, no one knows
It's not even on the news, really.
Anyway, I get it.
yes, thank you
Oh, good job
Oh, it's really him.
I don't want to sound regretful, Mr.
Rep.
To the president of the Changni-dong women’s association
I got a call
What, who? Changni-dong father and daughter...
Namyeon Jeong?
What is he calling for?
To the congressman
I have a favor to ask of you.
Yeah?
What do you regret?
What is that?
The Kiyun City accident you mentioned
This is the bomb ingredient analysis table.
Oh my, my
Wow
Hmm?
IC
Oh my, we
Rep. I
Why are you calling me?
Insisting that it was butane gas
I wondered why they covered it up so quickly
You were doing a good job.
What kind of bullshit is this?
HMX detection
Characteristics of Korean C4’s unique blend
Only domestic military factories
It's a combination method.
Well, would you like me to read it all line by line?
They said we were in the same boat.
Why are you stabbing me in the back?
This is military supplies stolen.
It's spinning, right?
Rep. me
I
Because I'm handling it well
Just wait a moment
What are you doing behind your back?
It doesn't matter
If you fly to the special tourist zone because of this,
I can't stand it
Don't let that happen
I'll take care of it!
Minister
Brother!
Minister, if you criticize me
Because it can work out
Fighting!
IC
Oh, just, just, just, tsk.
Mistress
Oh my
Oh, sister, what's going on?
Did you come alone?
When I fall down, my nose touches me.
Do you come alone? Who do you come with?
- Ah...
- Take this.
What is this?
Seaweed soup?
Oh my, this is my favorite
I heard a lot of mussels...
But
What day is it today?
It was the day I saw Minseo.
daughter
Have you forgotten the day you lost your hearing?
Oh, do you remember Minseo’s birthday?
My parents are far away
There is no one to cook for me after giving birth.
After crying
Then 37 days
I made seaweed soup for you.
Why can't I remember?
Wow
You all remembered our Heeja unnie.
Is that your bank manager’s?
Oh, to give it to Myeong-oh.
Uh, Myeong-oh’s mom?
Yesterday I came to the laundromat
Myeong-oh was hit all hundred times.
How much did you boast about it?
Raising a child alone is so cruel
Just wait and see, he goes to Korea University.
uh
Brother, over there, that
I'll get it to you
I'll come later, Myeong-oh's mom
I decided to take a quick look
Oh, do you want to?
- Yes
Hey there
Are you going to the laundromat?
come with me
Let me get some air too
I have to do business, where can I come from?
Baby, just come back soon.
- Huh?
- Let's go, let's go.
Heeja!
What if I leave without saying anything?
You've been looking for it for a while
Why are you looking for me?
I looked for it because I wanted to see it.
Shall we go?
Yeah
Go
- Uh
- Let's go, sister.
us
When going outside
Shall we talk to each other and leave?
Brother, I'm here
Hey, I brought some side dishes.
Hey, Heeja.
Bring it to your brother.
I also boiled seaweed soup for you.
fish oil
Let's see
Wow
Just looking at the side dish container
Who came and went
I understand everything, I understand everything
Hey, if you don’t have an appetite,
Even with water
You must eat rice...
Oh no
Oh my, this sister is really
Eat it quickly
I'm not leaving until I eat all of this.
Why?
Is the seasoning not right?
Too hot? huh?
Ah...
Oh no
No, no, no.
This, grab a little bit of this
Huh? Now
What is this?
at the bus company
They brought it for me to sign.
If you sign there,
Why did our Myung-oh die?
young
I don't think you know
don't do it
Don't do it, don't do it
me too
Myeong-oh, I can’t let you go like this.
Don't do this
Let's not do it
Yeah, don't do it.
Come in
The day Kim In-seop was captured
707 is on a counter-terrorism mission
It's true that I left
Who's in charge of the operation?
The person in charge is the battalion commander.
I received a direct call from the Minister.
It is said that it was carried out
Inseop Kim
Where did you take me?
That's it
707 returned to the unit.
There were no other people
The military is not a service
He asked me to find out
Total 60 6789 vehicles
Logistics Support Group Colonel Jang Jun-hee
It's a unit vehicle.
Find out about Unit 707’s return route.
On the way, drive towards Jang Jun-hee.
They probably stole Kim In-seop away.
yes, i understand
sit down
this video
Where did you get it?
Please call a lawyer.
Inseop Kim
I'll ask again
The accident vehicle is gone.
The blackbox video inside was
It came from that computer.
The accident vehicle disappeared
How did you know?
from there
You didn't take it, did you?
Traffic accident at Giyun intersection
The article called Bomb
You posted it on the internet, right?
Who is behind it?
Terrorist organization?
North Korea?
Are you in politics?
Hey, this
It's miraculous logic.
Ah, it's been like this so far
Turn it over and take it
You made a spy and did it.
About me
I'm a reporter
I did some research.
I wasn't ordered to do it.
We did some research!
You are full of passion
Because I have a lot of time
Let's go slowly
Didn't anyone come?
Ah...
Producer Kim In-seop
I think I'll find it soon
Hey, how?
I decided to get information from JDD.
- JDD?
- Oh, what a surprise.
Why are you out there?
Oh, hey, I need your computer.
I asked you to look at it.
uh
Anyway, I'm looking for it there.
You will be contacted soon
Then I will come pick you up.
Hey, let's go together
Brother
I will go with you too.
Whoa, I'll go alone.
Why are we embarrassed?
no, it's dangerous
This time I'll go alone
Oh, sure...
Why is it suddenly quiet when I come?
We were quiet the whole time
- Right?
- Yes
Sorry, I'm late.
- Hehe, what time is it now?
-Why come now!
- You should go early, Jeonghwan.
- I waited!
Everyone is waiting for the adults
Is it okay then?
- Yeah.
- Wow, really.
I'm sorry
- That's it, man, okay
- Yes
I watched it all night
There wasn't anything special about the local cameras.
Hey, Jeonghwan
Ah, yes, mother.
In my case
I talked to a lawyer.
I got involved with the military
They say there's nothing good about it
Hey, Police Officer Park too
This neighborhood is safe
They said they were going to apply for a job in another town.
They said there was no report
To people I know
I tried calling back.
There was nothing useful
That one must have been done meticulously too.
Yeah
Then we are more precise than that.
Shouldn't we do something?
Sure, I have to do it.
too
Don't worry, sister.
Yeah yeah
Hey, we have the strongest...
Well, you work for an insurance company, uh.
Hey, something like actual cost insurance
Did you put them all in one by one?
To that extent we
Well, there's nothing to worry about.
Everyone is fearless, huh?
Even after seeing PD Kim being arrested,
I was just talking about uploading a video.
So what if something happens?
What should I do?
Isn't it obvious?
Hey
You saw me getting caught
Are you going to stay still?
uh
I'm coming to save you
This shit, shit
By the way, are you saving me?
Would that happen?
goodbye
younger brother
Are you upset?
I'm upset, I'm upset, oh my
True
Be sure to stop by before you go to work tomorrow
All you need is this
Torda, Thor
Honey, come out quickly!
Honey, Doyeon’s kindergarten bag
Where are you?
Is it the bag your wife mentioned?
Is this it?
yes, that's right
Doyeon, wake up, let’s go.
Come to work
here
charlotte sullivan
for death incident
After the Supreme Court ruling
Giyun City IT Special Zone...
Huh? It's the ice cream guy.
What ice cream?
That guy
gave me ice cream
for death incident
The legal process has ended...
Oh my, Choi Do-yeon
Without restoring trust
The position is that investment is difficult.
Experts said this announcement
In fact, in the Giyun City special district project,
As a signal to let go
I am interpreting
hello
Oh my, you tied your hair up nicely.
- Doyeonah
- Huh?
The man who appeared on TV
To the real Doyeon
Are you sure you gave me ice cream?
Yeah
similar-looking
Isn't it someone else?
No, it's him.
They look the same
Ah, then
That guy only told Doyeon
Did you give me ice cream?
Or to other kids too
I don't know that
He said it was given to me by my dad.
Oh, really?
uh? It's Olivia Teacher!
oh
My dad speaks English well!
Ah, what can I do with this much?
I have to go to work, see you later.
hello
Are you ready to have fun?
Be sure to stop by
Oh, are you here?
uh
Kim In-seop received PD position.
I'm going to go get it now.
Hey, that
Can I really go alone?
This
Take this
This is a tiny camera.
I also added GPS
Is this why you called me?
Just wait
Take it
So you came out early?
Yeah, well, it's a lot of work.
Maybe
Is this something I need to know?
no
just personally
yes
Come in
ha
Those again
What are you talking about like that?
uh
The atmosphere is a bit strong
Clean up the scene
Wow, that's crazy
Really, Mr. Just
Ah, Mr.
Fish oil, damn it, really, Mr.
Really, Mr.
Mr., you crazy, really, Mr.
Ah! Really, man, I'm going crazy, really
Hey, let's eat some food, you bastard, really!
Ha, Mr.
Brother, how are you?
What about me, I always live hard
Little brother, how are you feeling?
Thanks to you, I'm okay...
It hurts
our company name
I blame and curse
Well, it’s not like that, is it?
Wow, are you swearing?
I hate swearing so much
So in summer
I don't even go near the beach.
Because of the beach
And I also take a bath
It's called a wooden tablet, bro.
Good, good, good, that's how it should be
By the way, it's a business name.
It's too hard for me
It's too easy for you
Won't you help me out?
If you don't like it, feel free to say it.
I'll come visit you again
Uh, no, bro.
Of course I have to help.
Thanks, brother
Ta-da
What is this, a gun?
kid, taser gun
The thing is, I modified it.
Self-defense tools sold on the market
It’s on a different level, huh?
Be careful because it's stronger than the police version.
If you get hit, you really go to the goal.
and
This is a kick
Once loaded
Can shoot three times in a row
like a gun
Kill it?
Protect me with this?
no
Protect the other person
Don't kill me, just stun me with this.
You're not JDD anymore
You should also think about your family
Work gets bigger
Fish oil, really, mr.
Huh?
Where are you going?
Hey, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Where am I?
Uh...
I don't think it's a highway
Oh, right?
What are you watching?
My cell phone, why?
So
What are you looking at?
Ah, well, I saw this and that.
What, uh, short videos?
Why did you come?
Oh, me, me?
I told you to come
Well, why, there was that camera yesterday.
Install it again
That's right, I came to get it.
Yeah
It seems to me
You two and Doyeon's dad
doing something
It seems like it is
Are you coming?
I went to pick up Minseo
Because I will come back again
Just wait here
yes
Miss, what should I do?
My sister is scary!
Yay, man
What's scary, huh?
You just have to go install the camera again.
an honest alibi
What are you doing? Go quickly
They told me to wait here
Oh, right, right, uh
Wow, Mr.
Hey, look.
Look at this
Uh, Minseo’s dad.
You take a taxi and pick up Minseo.
I have some business to run for a moment.
uh
Minseo’s mother!
are you okay?
Yes, chase after me, quickly.
Uh, yeah
Clean up the scene
failed
Hey, you piece of trash.
You did that one thing right...
Hey
김인섭이
처리해
처리, 처...
죽여 버리라고, 이 새끼야
그래, 이 새끼야
진짜, 인마, 진짜로!
Please, please, okay? without a trace
do well
Ah, Mr.
Wow! I couldn't believe it
This really works, huh?
Drag me out
Wait a minute, wait a minute
Wait a minute
Where am I going?
No, where are you going...
Where are you going, okay?
Oh, where are we going?
Where are you going?
No, where are you going?
Oh, why don't you tell me, why!
Okay, ah...
I got it, kinda! Mr.
Hey, this is what you guys are doing now
Do you know how wrong it is?
Wait, wait, wait!
What is this, here?
Where are you?
quiet
No, no, no.
Uh, no, no.
PD Kim, I...
Now
Mr. Choi Kang
I rescued you
I'll take the coordinates
Let's go there
Because it's the safest place right now.
Okay
yes
I confirmed that there was no follow-up.
If you check the vehicle,
Won't it catch up soon?
It's okay, this isn't my car.
But are you hurt anywhere?
yes
But where is it?
It looks like a military facility used to collect information.
I guess I'm not using it anymore
yes
Hey, what are you doing?
Me?
yes
Didn't I tell you?
I'm holding on to insurance.
Not the sales side, but SIU
Insurance Fraud Investigation Team
I belong there.
No, it's not like that.
What is it really like?
Um...
Neighbor or cousin?
yes?
Have you been there, brother?
You waited a long time, right?
No, no
You arrived in the blink of an eye
Wow, our mutual brother’s face is so cool
It's a cute statue
Ah
thank you for today
Uh, sorry, sorry.
Uh, let's get in.
yes
Are the car keys in your car?
Ah, yes, brother.
It's inside
proceed carefully
No, why is this GPS not this way?
Are you going towards Seoul?
Oh, really
Didn't something happen?
What happened?
Oh, it's really too much, really.
Ah, really why
Why do you keep surprising people?
What, why, what, again?
You just said what happened to the GPS?
Me?
- Did I do that?
- No, oh
What's going on?
Oh, well, there is.
take it
Oh, I'll get it.
Take it
Oh, you can get it, you will get it.
Uh, what's going on at this hour?
What could happen?
Successfully complete the mission
I'm on my way back
Oh, you're leaving work?
I thought it was just my knees that were bad
Are your ears bad too?
Oh, I need to pray
That, PD Kim
So that I can come back safely
Gotta pray, uh
I'll send you the address, come there.
Uh, okay, okay.
Hey, have a nice day off work.
What are you saying?
Did you see it? Choi Kang got off work
Did you hear everything?
Don't lie!
What kind of Somers are you?
Oh my, it's me, really
Ah...
I heard it all
It's a place no one knows
You'll be able to buy some time for a while.
of two repositories
Take the drum in the right storage bin.
If you push it to the side
you will see a door
What is this all about?
You worked hard
It may be uncomfortable, but
stay here for a while
It will be safe.
How far are you going?
Be quiet, please
Ah, quickly...
Please hurry up, really.
Is this right here, bro?
Isn’t it a strange place?
uh?
Uh, hey, PD Kim
Oh, that's why
I tried to come alone...
-Why?
- uh?
what?
Are we strangers?
A
Much closer than others
That's right, brother
Oh, right, right
We are that...
like family
I'm your cousin
Did you hear?
These local people are like family.
yes
Give it to me, brother.
I'll take a look
Ah, I'm on the right track.
Where are you going?
Ah, just go to work, to work
Around there...
I knew it would be like this
I got it right, these, really
Namyeon is
Make me work alone at the supermarket
I knew it would be like this
Just got caught, you guys
Huh?
uh? Are you sure you came here?
uh?
strange
Where did they go?
uh?
Namyeon!
honey!
Damn man!
Uh, yeah
Ah, fun, hey, fun.
It's so fun
Come out because it’s so fun
Really now
Stop playing around and come out now
Uh, I won't be angry.
Uh, it's okay
Baby, because I can't sleep
Come out quickly and join us
Uh, let's talk.
Where are you?
AC
You're making me feel bad, really, Mr.
The person who stole the bomb
Who are you?
Quite a big guy
Do you think they are related?
Here and there
There was a rumor that he was wandering around.
Ah, in this wide place
How do you find that little button?
Shall we begin?
If you find the location
Do you want to go right in?
Do I have plans for dinner tomorrow?
Cancel
After moving here
It's really strange
Brother, what is the operation?
Kim In-seop and
Because they seem to be related
Have the kids do a background check.
Byungnam's older brother and Namyeon's older sister
No answer!
I fell behind
Subtitle: Jang Se-ri